Finding Aid for School of Public Health (University of Michigan) Records 1909-2015 (bulk 1941-2006).
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Office Files, 1940-2005
  - Files, 1982-2005
    - Council on Education for Public Health (CEPH) Accreditation
      The Council for Education for Public Health (CEPH) Accreditation series, 0.5 linear feet, documents the school's ongoing efforts to ensure that they are meeting standards in education set by the CEPH. Included are records documenting site visits by CEPH officials, CEPH Board of Councilors' meeting supporting documents, and correspondence related to accreditation review.
      - Accreditation Site Visit, March 30-April 1, 1992 (Box 83)
      - Board of Councilor's Meeting, June 9, 2000 (Box 83)
      - Correspondence
        - 1992-1997, 9 folders (Box 96)
          [PR RESTRICTED until July 1 2027 ]
        - 2000, 6 folders (Box 97)
          [PR RESTRICTED until July 1 2030 ]
    - Budget, 1974-2005
      The Budget sub-subseries consists of 1.8 linear feet, and provides detailed evidence of the financial operations of the school between 1974 and 2005. The relative importance of federal and foundation support is manifest in these records. Included are budget requests, projections, actuals, and budget meeting minutes.
      - Budget Material
        - Budget, 1987-1988 (Box 88)
        - Budget, 1989-1990 (Box 88)
        - Budget Material, 1991-1992 (Box 88)
        - Budget Planning, 1992-1993 (Box 88)
        - Budget, 1993-1994 (Box 88)
        - Budget, 1994-1995 (Box 88)
        - Budget, 1995-1996 (Box 88)
        - Budget, 1996-1997 (Box 88)
        - Budget, 1999 (Box 88)
        - Budget, 2000 (Box 88)
        - Budget, 2001-2002 (Box 88)
        - Budget, 2002-2003 (Box 88)
        - Budget, 2003-2004 (Box 88)
        - Budget, 2004-2005 (Box 89)
      - Budget Projections (Box 89)
      - Comparative Salary Analyses, 1974-1975 (Box 89)
      - File on Budget Materials (Statements and Background Materials -- Chronological Order) (Box 89)
      - Meetings
        - Budget Conference, April 28, 1987 (Box 89)
        - Budget Meeting, March 16, 1989 (Box 89)
        - Budget Meeting, March 9, 1990; 2 folders (Box 89)
        - Budget Meeting, February 14, 1991 (Box 89)
        - Budget Conference, 1997-1998 (Box 89)
        - Budget Meeting, March 24, 1998 (Box 89)
        - Budget Meeting, April 1, 1999 (Box 89)
        - Budget Meeting, March 14, 2000 (Box 89)
        - Budget Meeting, February 20, 2001 (Box 89)
      - Memoranda
        - Memoranda on Budgetary Issues, 1983-1984 (Box 89)
        - Memoranda on Budgetary Issues, 1982 (Box 89)
        - Memoranda on Budgetary Issues, 1981-1996 (Box 89)
    - Collaborative Agreements, 1982-1989
      The Collaborative Agreements sub-subseries, 1982-1989, .5 linear feet, documents the School of Public Health's effort to foster an environment of collaboration, mutual understanding, and reciprocity between itself and other educational institutions throughout the world. Included are collaborative agreements arrived at between the University of Michigan School of Public Health and institutions in: Spain, Lebanon, India, China, Egypt, Jordan, Saudi Arabia, China, and Mexico.
      - Signing of Collaborative Agreement, March 25-April 1, 1989 (Box 90)
      - UM SPH/Madrid Cusp Project (Box 90)
      - Affiliation between American University of Beirut and School of Public Health, 1982 (Box 90)
      - Collaboration in Support of Palestinian Public Health (Box 90)
      - Bhopal Letter of Intent, 1985 (Box 90)
      - Scholarly Exchange Programs with Shanghai First Medical College and Kunming Medical College (Box 90)
      - Egyptian Study Group, 1980 (Box 90)
      - Affiliation Program with Yarmouk University, Jordan (Box 90)
      - Historical Center for Health Sciences (Box 90)
      - Sebai Institute, Collaboration (Box 90)
      - Collaboration Agreement with the Ministry of Health Mexico (Box 90)
      - Futures Committee (Box 90)
    - Committees, 1964-1993
      The sub-subseries, Committees, 3.0 feet, contains the official set of Executive Committee minutes dating from 1964 through 1993. Also included are the Faculty Meeting Minutes for the years 1964 through 2000 and the Executive Committee Actions for the years 1977 through 1990. These records richly illustrate school-wide administrative issues and policy decisions. Scattered minutes and related material will also be found within the annual files in the dean's subgroups.
      - Executive Committee and Faculty Meetings
        - Executive Committee and Faculty Meeting Minutes
          - 1964-1970, 6 folders (Box 90)
          - 1971-1973, 3 folders (Box 91)
        - Executive Committee Meeting Minutes, 1974 (Box 91)
        - Faculty Meeting Minutes, 1974 (Box 91)
        - Executive Committee and Faculty Meeting Minutes, 1975 (Box 91)
        - Faculty Meeting Minutes, 1976 (Box 91)
        - Executive Committee Minutes, 1976-1978; 2 folders (Box 91)
        - Faculty Meeting Minutes (Box 92)
          - 1977-1981, 2 folders (Box 92)
          - 1982-1986, 2 folders (Box 92)
          - 1987-1992, 2 folders (Box 92)
          - 1993-2000, 2 folders (Box 92)
        - Executive Committee Minutes
          - 1979-1980, 2 folders (Box 92)
          - 1980-1982 (Box 92)
          - 1982-1986, 2 folders (Box 93)
          - 1987-1993 (Box 93)
        - Executive Committee Actions
          - 1977-1989 (Box 93)
          - 1990 (Box 93)
    - Reorganization, 1993-1995
      The Reorganization subseries, 15 linear feet, includes a SPH Review Committee report and correspondence documenting reorganization that occurred as a result of the review committee's findings.
      - Meeting the Health Challenges of a New Era: Report of the School of Public Health Review Committee, The University of Michigan, March 17, 1994 (Box 93)
      - Correspondence
        - 1993 (Box 97)
          [PR RESTRICTED until July 1 2023 ]
        - 1994 (Box 97)
          [PR RESTRICTED until July 1 2024 ]
        - 1995-1996 (Box 97)
          [PR RESTRICTED until July 1 2026 ]
    - Student Recruitment, 1988-2001
      The Student Recruitment sub-subseries, 0.7 linear feet, contains records covering the period from 1988 to 2001. The sub-subseries deals with matters pertaining to enrollment, academic outreach, the On Job Off Campus (OJOC) program, and diversity initiatives. Also included is a run of enrollment meeting minutes, 1992-1995.
      - Enrollment Meetings
        - January 24, 1992 (Box 93)
        - February 2, 1993 (Box 93)
        - January 10, 1994 (Box 93)
        - December 8, 1994 (Box 93)
        - December 12, 1995 (Box 93)
      - Office of Academic Outreach (David Pearlman) (Box 93)
      - On Job Off Campus Funding, 1995-1999 (Box 93)
      - Racial/Cultural Concerns Task Force, 1988-1990 (Box 94)
      - Racial/Cultural Concerns Task Force II (Box 94)
      - The Robert Wood Johnson Foundation, Health and Society Scholars Program, Proposal for Planning Process, 2001 (Box 94)
    - Miscellaneous, 1979; 1987
      The Miscellaneous sub-subseries, 0.2 linear feet, contains just a few stray items that did not seem to be a part of any larger whole within the accession. The first file in this sub-subseries, Preventive Medicine Residency Program, 1979, should be accessed with the understanding that material that provides its context resides in Box 32. Box 59 contains material that will help place the second file, Strategic Planning Retreat, April 3, 1987 in context.
      - Preventive Medicine Residency Program (See also Box 32), 1979 (Box 94)
      - Strategic Planning Retreat, April 3, 1987(See also Box 59) (Box 94)
    - Population Planning and International Health (PPIH), 1979-1993
      The Population Planning and International Health sub-subseries, 0.5 linear feet, contains records documenting the 1993 proposed moratorium on Population Planning and International Health faculty recruitment and student admissions. A special review committee convened to assess the situation and determined that the decision to enact the moratorium was arrived at outside the parameters of normal university protocol, and that the criteria cited for closure of the program did not align with the University's Standard Practice Guide. The committee recommended that the moratorium be lifted and the department not be closed. As a result, June Osborne announced her resignation as Dean effective September 1st, 1993, at which time Richard G. Cornell assumed his role as interim Dean of the School of Public Health.
      - International Health Ad Hoc Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 94)
      - PPIH Closure, Freedom of information Act Requests, Etc., 1993 (Box 94)
      - PPIH Review Background (Box 94)
      - PPIH Review Committee (Box 94)
      - PPIH Moratorium Background (Box 94)
      - PPIH Moratorium Correspondence (Box 94)
      - Restructure of PPIH, 1985
- Dean Richard Remington, 1969-1981
  The Dean Richard Remington (1974-1981) series comprises the next twelve linear feet of the collection (Boxes 25-36). Like the materials in the Dean Myron E. Wegman series, these records are annual files arranged into six subseries: Administration, American Public Health Association, Committees, Correspondence, Departments, and Programs. The American Public Health Association files do not extend past 1974, reflecting the end of Remington's active involvement. The Programs subseries comes to be incorporated under the department rubric, under Community Health Services, as the school reorganized its administrative structure in 1978. This internal realignment reflects the school's efforts to present a comprehensive curriculum in the face of increasing diversification of specialties in the field of public health. Remington's Administration and Committees files are more detailed and more comprehensive than are Wegman's files. They provide an informative source on the perils of running a school during times of shrinking Federal and state funding for public health education. Especially illuminating are the accreditation reviews of 1975 and 1980, instances in which the school subjected its program to the rigors of peer review. As was the case with the Wegman materials, the Remington Correspondence was significantly altered from its original order based on geography to a month-by-month chronological sequence.
  - Annual Files, 1974
    - Administration
      - General, 1974 (Box 24)
      - Annual Reports, 1973-1974; 2 folders (Box 24)
      - Department Chairs Review, 1971-1974 (Box 24)
      - Library, 1974 (Box 24)
      - Memoranda (department heads), 1974 (Box 24)
      - Memoranda (faculty), 1974 (Box 24)
      - Public Health Alumni Society, 1974 (Box 24)
      - Reorganization of SPH, 1974; 3 folders (Box 24)
      - Student Affairs Director Search, 1974 (Box 24)
      - Students, 1974 (Box 24)
    - American Public Health Association
      - General, 1974 (Box 24)
      - Annual Meeting (New Orleans), 1974 (Box 24)
    - Committees
      - General (student participation), 1969-1974 (Box 24)
      - Advisory Committee on Academic Rank, 1974 (Box 24)
      - Affirmative Action for Women, 1973-1975 (Box 24)
      - Criteria (for assessing programs), 1973-1974 (Box 24)
        (see Program and Curriculum Review)
      - Executive, 1974; 2 folders (Box 25)
      - Extension/Continuing Education, 1974 (Box 25)
      - Human Studies, 1974 (Box 25)
      - Program and Curriculum Review, 1974 (Box 25)
    - Correspondence
      - 1974, 6 folders (Box 25)
    - Departments
      - Biostatistics (R. Cornell), 1974 (Box 25)
      - Community Health (A. Brown and C. Wylie), 1974; 2 folders (Box 25)
      - Environmental and Industrial Health, 1974 (Box 25)
      - Epidemiology (F. Davenport), 1974 (Box 25)
      - Medical Care Organization (Feingold), 1974 (Box 25)
      - Population Planning Center (L. Corsa), 1974 (Box 25)
    - Programs
      - Community Mental Health (L. Baler), 1974 (Box 25)
      - Dental Public Health (D. Striffler), 1974 (Box 25)
      - Health Behavior (I. Rosenstock), 1974 (Box 25)
      - Health Education (S. Simonds), 1974 (Box 25)
      - Health Planning (R. Grosse), 1974 (Box 25)
      - Hospital Administration (J. Griffith), 1974 (Box 25)
      - Maternal and Child Health (R. Meyer), 1974 (Box 25)
      - Nutrition (J. Robson), 1972-1974 (Box 25)
      - Public Health Nursing (L. Ostrand), 1974 (Box 25)
  - Annual Files, 1975
    - Administration
      - General, 1975 (Box 25)
      - Accreditation
        - Self Study, 1974-1975 (Box 25)
        - Site Visit Report, 1975 (Box 25)
        - APHA Council on Education, 1975 (Box 25)
        - Responses to APHA Report, 1975 (Box 25)
      - Annual Reports, 1974-1975; 2 folders (Box 26)
      - Assistant Dean (M. Cardin), 1975 (Box 26)
      - Associate Dean (H. Magnuson), 1975 (Box 26)
      - Blood Pressure Control Conference, 1975 (Box 26)
      - Continuing Education, 1975 (Box 26)
      - Library, 1975 (Box 26)
      - Memoranda (department heads), 1975 (Box 26)
      - Memoranda (faculty), 1975 (Box 26)
      - Nursing Health Services (proposal to Kellogg Foundation), 1975 (Box 26)
      - Primary Care Planning Study, 1975 (Box 26)
      - Public Health Alumni Society, 1975 (Box 26)
      - Students, 1975
        - Black Student Organization, 1975 (Box 26)
        - Food Action Coalition, 1975 (Box 26)
        - GEO Liaison (W. Work), 1975 (Box 26)
        - Public Health Association, 1974-1975 (Box 26)
    - Committees
      - Advisory Committee on Academic Rank, 1975 (Box 26)
      - Affirmative Action for Women, 1975 (Box 26)
      - Computer, 1975 (Box 26)
      - Core Review (MPH), 1975 (Box 26)
      - Executive, 1975 (Box 26)
      - Faculty Meetings, 1975 (Box 26)
      - Human Studies, 1975 (Box 26)
      - Occupational Health and Safety, 1975 (Box 26)
      - Program and Curriculum Review, 1975 (Box 26)
    - Correspondence
      - 1975, 6 folders (Box 26)
    - Departments
      - Biostatistics (R. Cornell), 1975 (Box 27)
      - Environmental and Industrial Health (M. Hilbert), 1975 (Box 27)
      - Epidemiology (F. Davenport), 1975
        - Research Center for Diseases of the Heart (Tecumseh Study), 1975 (Box 27)
      - Medical Care Organization (Feingold), 1975 (Box 27)
      - Population Planning Center (L. Corsa), 1975 (Box 27)
    - Programs
      - Community Health (L. Baler), 1975 (Box 27)
      - Dental Public Health (D. Striffler), 1975 (Box 27)
      - Health Behavior (I. Rosenstock), 1975 (Box 27)
      - Health Planning and Administration, 1975 (Box 27)
      - Hospital Administration (J. Griffith), 1975 (Box 27)
      - Maternal and Child Health (R. Meyer), 1975 (Box 27)
      - Nutrition (F. Larkin), 1975 (Box 27)
      - Public Health Nursing (L. Ostrand), 1975 (Box 27)
  - Annual Files, 1976
    - Administration
      - General, 1976 (Box 27)
      - Annual Reports, 1975-1976; 2 folders (Box 27)
      - Assistant Dean (Cardin), 1976; 2 folders (Box 27)
      - Blood Pressure Control Conference, 1975-1976 (Box 27)
      - Budgets, 1974-1976 (Box 27)
      - Library, 1976 (Box 27)
      - Memoranda (department heads), 1976 (Box 27)
      - Memoranda (faculty), 1976 (Box 27)
      - Public Health Alumni Society, 1976 (Box 27)
      - Students, 1976 (Box 27)
    - Committees
      - General, 1976 (Box 27)
      - Advisory Committee on Academic Rank, 1976 (Box 27)
      - Affirmative Action for Women, 1976 (Box 27)
      - Continuing Education/Extension, 1976 (Box 27)
      - Executive, 1976; 2 folders (Box 27)
      - Faculty Meetings, 1976 (Box 28)
      - Health Service Administration (MPH/Ph.D Review), 1975-1976; 2 folders (Box 28)
      - Human Studies, 1976 (Box 28)
      - Program and Curriculum Review, 1976 (Box 28)
      - Student Affairs, 1976 (Box 28)
    - Correspondence
      - 1976, 6 folders (Box 28)
    - Departments
      - Biostatistics (R. Cornell), 1976 (Box 28)
      - Environmental and Industrial Health (M. Hilbert), 1976; 2 folders (Box 28)
      - Epidemiology (F. Davenport), 1976 (Box 28)
      - Medical Care Organization (Feingold), 1976 (Box 28)
      - Population Planning Center (L. Corsa), 1976 (Box 28)
    - Programs
      - Community Health (L. Baler), 1976 (Box 28)
      - Dental Public Health (D. Striffler), 1976 (Box 28)
      - Health Behavior (I. Rosenstock), 1976 (Box 28)
      - Health Gerontology, 1976 (Box 28)
      - Health Planning and Administration (J. Romani), 1976; 2 folders (Box 28)
      - Hospital Administration (J. Griffith), 1976 (Box 28)
      - Maternal and Child Health, 1976 (Box 28)
      - Nutrition (F. Larkin), 1976 (Box 28)
      - Public Health Nursing (L. Ostrand), 1976 (Box 28)
  - Annual Files, 1977
    - Administration
      - General, 1977 (Box 28)
      - Annual Reports, 1976-1977; 2 folders (Box 28)
      - Assistant Dean (M. Cardin), 1977 (Box 28)
      - Continuing Education Seminars, 1977 (Box 28)
      - Human Environmental Health Assessment, 1977 (Box 28)
      - Library, 1977 (Box 28)
      - Memoranda (department heads), 1977 (Box 28)
      - Memoranda (faculty), 1977 (Box 29)
      - Population Planning Review, 1974-1977
        - Background, 1974-1975; 2 folders (Box 29)
        - Review, 1976-1977; 2 folders (Box 29)
      - Public Health Alumni Society, 1977 (Box 29)
      - Students, 1977 (Box 29)
    - Committees
      - General, 1977 (Box 29)
      - Advisory Committee on Academic Rank, 1977 (Box 29)
      - Advisory Committee on Continuing Medical Education, 1977 (Box 29)
      - Executive, 1977; 2 folders (Box 29)
      - Faculty Meetings, 1977 (Box 29)
      - Graduate Requirements in Public Health (GRIPH), 1976-1977 (Box 29)
      - Health Services Administration (MHSA), 1977 (Box 29)
      - Human Studies, 1977 (Box 29)
      - Student Affairs, 1977 (Box 29)
    - Correspondence
      - 1977, 10 folders (Box 29)
    - Departments
      - Biostatistics (R. Cornell), 1977 (Box 30)
      - Environmental and Industrial Health (M. Hilbert), 1977
        - NIOSH, 1977 (Box 30)
      - Epidemiology (G. Payne), 1977; 2 folders
        - Tecumseh Study Questionnaires, 1977 (Box 30)
      - Medical Care Organization (Feingold), 1977 (Box 30)
      - Population Planning Center (L. Corsa), 1977 (Box 30)
    - Programs
      - Community Health (L. Baler), 1977 (Box 30)
      - Dental Public Health (D. Striffler), 1977 (Box 30)
      - Health Behavior (I. Rosenstock), 1977 (Box 30)
      - Health Gerontology (T. Hickey), 1977 (Box 30)
      - Health Planning (J. Romani), 1977 (Box 30)
      - Hospital Administration (J. Griffith), 1977 (Box 30)
      - Nutrition, 1977 (Box 30)
      - Public Health Nursing (L. Ostrand), 1977 (Box 30)
  - Annual Files, 1978
    - Administration
      - General, 1978 (Box 30)
      - Annual Reports, 1977-1978; 2 folders (Box 30)
      - Assistant Dean (M. Cardin), 1978 (Box 30)
      - Memoranda (department heads), 1978 (Box 30)
      - Memoranda (faculty), 1978 (Box 30)
      - Project Grant Proposals, 1978; 3 folders (Box 30)
      - Public Health Alumni Society, 1978 (Box 30)
      - Students, 1978 (Box 30)
    - Committees
      - General, 1977-1978 (Box 30)
      - Advisory Committee on Academic Rank, 1978 (Box 30)
      - Affirmative Action for Women, 1978 (Box 30)
      - Continuing Education, 1978 (Box 30)
      - Curriculum, 1978 (Box 30)
      - Executive, 1978; 2 folders (Box 31)
      - Faculty Meetings, 1978 (Box 31)
      - GRIPH, 1978 (Box 31)
      - Human Studies, 1978 (Box 31)
      - Student Affairs, 1978 (Box 31)
    - Correspondence
      - 1978, 9 folders (Box 31)
    - Departments/Divisions
      - Biostatistics (R. Cornell), 1978 (Box 31)
      - Community Health Programs (L. Baler and D. Striffler), 1978
        - Community Mental Health (D. Smith), 1978 (Box 31)
        - Health Gerontology (T. Hickey), 1978 (Box 31)
        - Maternal and Child Health, 1978 (Box 31)
        - Nutrition (G. Owen), 1978 (Box 31)
      - Environmental and Industrial Health, 1978 (Box 31)
      - Epidemiology (F. Payne and V. Hawthorne), 1978; 2 folders (Box 31)
      - Health Behavior (I. Rosenstock), 1978 (Box 31)
      - Health Planning (J. Romani), 1978 (Box 31)
      - Hospital Administration (J. Griffith), 1978 (Box 31)
      - Medical Care Organization (R. Bashshur and R. Penchansky), 1978 (Box 31)
      - Population Planning Center (J. Finkle and Y. Takeshita), 1978 (Box 31)
      - Population Planning Program (G. Simmons and T. Poffenburger), 1978 (Box 31)
  - Annual Files, 1979
    - Administration
      - General, 1979 (Box 32)
      - Annual Reports, 1978-1979 (Box 32)
      - Center for Continuing Education (P. Dual), 1978-1979; 4 folders (Box 32)
      - Library, 1979 (Box 32)
      - Memoranda (department heads), 1979 (Box 32)
      - Memoranda (faculty), 1979 (Box 32)
      - Preventive Medicine Residency, 1979 (Box 32)
      - Public Health alumni Society, 1979 (Box 32)
      - Students, 1979 (Box 32)
    - Committees
      - General, 1979 (Box 32)
      - Advisory Committee on Academic Rank, 1979 (Box 32)
      - Affirmative Action for Women, 1979 (Box 32)
      - Continuing Medical Education, 1979 (Box 32)
      - Curriculum, 1979 (Box 32)
      - Executive, 1979; 2 folders (Box 32)
    - Correspondence
      - 1979, 6 folders (Box 32)
    - Departments
      - Biostatistics (R. Cornell and L. Verbrugge), 1979; 2 folders (Box 32)
      - Community Health (D. Striffler), 1979
        - Dental Public Health, 1979 (Box 32)
        - Health Gerontology, 1979 (Box 32)
        - Maternal and Child Health (Box 32)
        - Nutrition, 1979 (Box 32)
      - Environmental and Industrial Health (M. Hilbert), 1979 (Box 33)
      - Epidemiology (V. Hawthorne and M. Julius), 1979; 2 folders (Box 33)
      - Health Behavior (I. Rosenstock), 1979 (Box 33)
      - Health Planning and Administration (J. Romani), 1979; 2 folders (Box 33)
      - Hospital Administration (J. Griffith), 1979 (Box 33)
      - Medical Care Organization (R. Bashshur), 1979 (Box 33)
      - Population Planning Center (J. Finkle), 1979 (Box 33)
      - Population Planning Program (G. Simmons and T. Poffenberger), 1979 (Box 33)
  - Annual Files, 1980
    - Administration
      - General, 1980 (Box 33)
      - Accreditation (ACEHSA and CEPH), 1979-1980
        - ACEHSA Site Visit Reports, 1980 (Box 33)
        - ACEHSA Departmental Surveys, 1980
          - Community Health (Box 33)
          - Health Planning and Administration (Box 33)
          - Hospital Administration (Box 33)
          - Medical Care Organization (Box 33)
          - Population Planning (Box 33)
        - UMSPH Self-Study, 1979-1980; 2 folders (Box 33)
      - Annual Reports, 1979-1980; 2 folders (Box 34)
      - Assistant Dean (M. Cardin), 1980 (Box 34)
      - Chippewa Health Study, 1978-1980 (Box 34)
      - Center for Continuing Education, 1980; 3 folders (Box 34)
      - Memoranda (department heads), 1980 (Box 34)
      - Memoranda (faculty), 1980 (Box 34)
      - Public Health Alumni Society, 1980 (Box 34)
      - Students, 1980 (Box 34)
    - Committees
      - General, 1980 (Box 34)
      - Advisory Committee on Academic Rank, 1980 (Box 34)
      - Affirmative Action for Women, 1980 (Box 34)
      - Continuing Medical Education, 1980 (Box 34)
      - Curriculum, 1980 (Box 34)
      - Executive, 1980; 2 folders (Box 34)
      - Faculty Meetings, 1980 (Box 34)
      - Human Studies, 1980 (Box 34)
    - Correspondence
      - 1980, 6 folders (Box 34)
    - Departments
      - Biostatistics (R. Cornell and L. Verbrugge), 1980; 3 folders (Box 35)
      - Community Health (D. Striffler), 1980
        - Child and Family Health (Falkner), 1980 (Box 35)
        - Community Mental Health (Baler), 1980 (Box 35)
        - Dental Public Health, 1980 (Box 35)
        - Health Gerontology (Hickey), 1980 (Box 35)
        - Human Nutrition (Owen), 1980 (Box 35)